(Alex:)All right. I will tell him you called.
- Hmm. That's weird.
- What?
(Amy:)Sheldon told me
he had a new assistant named Alex.
(Amy:)He didn't mention that Alex was a girl.
(Penny:)Maybe he didn't notice.
(Amy:)You're right.
I don't have to worry about Sheldon.
(Penny:)No, you do not.
(Amy:)It's her I have to worry about.
(Penny:)Oh. Amy, really?
She is not gonna come on to Sheldon.
(Amy:)Oh, really?
(Amy:)Look at this face.
(Amy:)How can any woman spend eight hours
a day alone with this face...
(Amy:)...and not fall in love with it?
(Penny:)Well, for starters, at some point,
that face starts talking.
(Penny:)Amy, this is crazy.
You have nothing to be suspicious about.
(Amy:)I'm not suspicious.
I just wanna stop in, say hi to my boyfriend,
and meet his new assistant.